<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>CIWS_ForestryBureauAuthorized (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.CIWSForestryBureauAuthorized</packageId>
  <author>topp2000</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/CIWSForestryBureauAuthorized</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of topp2000s mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=946746541

- Fixed outdoor beauty

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/CIWSForestryBureauAuthorized][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Add plants: Iron Tree, Silver Tree, Golden Tree, Plasteel Tree, Component Tree, Uranium Tree, fast-growing poplar.
Add technology: Forestry Bureau authorizes A (LinYeJuShouQuanA), forestry bureau authorizes B (LinYeJuShouQuanB).
Iron Tree: growth period 5 days, harvest: Steel, harvest yield:80, need technology: forestry authority A (LinYeJuShouQuanA).
Silver Tree: growth period 5 days, harvest: Silver, harvest yield:6, need technology: forestry authority A (LinYeJuShouQuanA).
Golden Tree: growth period 5 days, harvest: Gold, harvest yield:1, need technology: forestry authority B (LinYeJuShouQuanB).
Plasteel Tree: growth period 10 days, harvest: Plasteel, harvest yield:15, need technology: forestry authority B (LinYeJuShouQuanB).
Component Tree: growth period 5 days, harvest: ComponentIndustrial, harvest yield:1, need technology: forestry authority B (LinYeJuShouQuanB).
Uranium Tree: growth period 5 days, harvest: Uranium, harvest yield:3, need technology: forestry authority B (LinYeJuShouQuanB).
Fast-growing poplar: growth period 5 days, harvest: WoodLog, harvest 75.
The Forestry Bureau authorized A (LinYeJuShouQuanA): the workload is 1500.
The Forestry Bureau authorized B (LinYeJuShouQuanB): the workload is 3000.

添加植物：铁树，银树，金树，玻璃钢树，机械树，铀树，速生杨。
添加科技：林业局授权A（LinYeJuShouQuanA），林业局授权B（LinYeJuShouQuanB）。
铁树：生长期5天，收获物：钢铁，收获数量80，需要科技：林业局授权A（LinYeJuShouQuanA）。
银树：生长期5天，收获物：白银，收获数量6，需要科技：林业局授权A（LinYeJuShouQuanA）。
金树：生长期5天，收获物：黄金，收获数量1，需要科技：林业局授权B（LinYeJuShouQuanB）。
玻璃钢树：生长期10天，收获物：玻璃钢，收获数量15，需要科技：林业局授权B（LinYeJuShouQuanB）。
机械树：生长期5天，收获物：机械零件，收获数量1，需要科技：林业局授权B（LinYeJuShouQuanB）。
铀树：生长期5天，收获物：铀，收获数量3，需要科技：林业局授权B（LinYeJuShouQuanB）。
速生杨：生长期5天，收获物：原木，收获数量75。
林业局授权A（LinYeJuShouQuanA）：工作量1500。
林业局授权B（LinYeJuShouQuanB）：工作量3000。

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]</description>
</ModMetaData>